wish.com 2017-10-30

# Wish | Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy Scope 

We at Wish know you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy. **By using or accessing the Services in any manner, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy, and you hereby consent that we will collect, use, and share your information in the following ways.** Remember that your use of Wish’s Services is at all times subject to the Terms of Use, which incorporates this Privacy Policy. Any terms we use in this Policy without defining them have the definitions given to them in the Terms of Use. 

What does this Privacy Policy cover? 

This Privacy Policy covers our treatment of personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") that we gather when you are accessing or using our Services, but not to the practices of companies we don’t own or control, or people that we don’t manage. We gather various types of Personal Information from our users, as explained in more detail below, and we use this Personal Information internally in connection with our Services, including to personalize, provide, and improve our services, to allow you to set up a user account and profile, to contact you and allow other users to contact you, to respond to your questions, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, to communicate service updates, offers, and promotions to you, and to analyze how you use the Services. In certain cases, we may also share some Personal Information with third parties, but only as described below. 

As noted in the Terms of Use, we do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register for the Services or send any personal information about yourself to us. Parents and legal guardians may not agree to this Privacy Policy or register for the Services on behalf of any children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that a child under 13 may have provided us personal information, please contact us at [privacy@contextlogic.com](mailto:privacy@contextlogic.com). 

Will Wish ever change this Privacy Policy? 

We’re constantly trying to improve our Services, so we may need to change this Privacy Policy from time to time as well, but we will alert you to changes by placing a notice on the Wish.com and/or WishWall.me websites, by sending you an email, and/or by some other means. Please note that if you’ve opted not to receive legal notice emails from us (or you haven’t provided us with your email address), those legal notices will still govern your use of the Services, and you are still responsible for reading and understanding them. If you use the Services after any changes to the Privacy Policy have been posted, that means you agree to all of the changes. 

What Information does Wish Collect? 

Information You Provide to Us 

We receive and store any information you knowingly provide to us. For example, when you use the Services, register or create an online account with or through the Services, provide information through your account settings, purchase products or services, request information from us, sign up for newsletters or our email list, use our service, enter into sweepstakes or other promotion, fill out a survey, request customer support, or otherwise communicate with or contact us, we may collect Personal Information such as your name, address, email address, phone number, billing and shipping information, and third-party account credentials (for example, your log-in credentials for Facebook). If you provide your Facebook or other third-party account credentials to us or otherwise sign in to the Services through a third party site or service, you understand some content and/or information in those accounts (“Third Party Account Information”) may be transmitted into your account with us, and that Third Party Account Information transmitted to our Services is covered by this Privacy Policy. For example, when you log in to the Services using your Facebook credentials, we receive certain of your personally identifiable information associated with your Facebook account. Certain information may be required to register with us or to take advantage of some of our features. 

We may communicate with you if you’ve provided us the means to do so. For example, if you’ve given us your email address or mobile phone number, we may send promotional communications of interest, such as via email, text message, or push notifications on your mobile device, from or about us, about our products and/or services, or about other promotional materials on behalf of our third party partners and affiliates who we think can offer services and products of interest to you, or email you about your use of the Services. Additionally, Also, we may receive a confirmation when you open an email from us. This confirmation helps us make our communications with you more interesting and improve our services. Please the “What Choices Do I Have” section below for opting out of communication from us. 

Information collected automatically 

Whenever you interact with our Services, we automatically receive and record information from your browser or device, which may include your IP address, geolocation data, device identification, “cookie” information, the type of browser and/or device you’re using to access our Services, and the page or feature you requested. “Cookies” are identifiers we transfer to your browser or device that allow us to recognize your browser or device and tell us how and when pages and features in our Services are visited and by how many people. You may be able to change the preferences on your browser or device to prevent or limit your device’s acceptance of cookies, but this may prevent you from taking advantage of some of our features. We also may collect information about your use of the Services, including the date and time you visit the Services, the areas or pages of the Services that you visit, the amount of time you spend viewing or using the Services, the number of times you return to the Services, other click-stream or site usage data, emails that you open, forward or click-through to our Site, and other sites that you may visit. 

Our advertising partners may also transmit cookies to your browser or device, when you click on ads that appear on the Services. Also, if you click on a link to a third party website or service, a third party may also transmit cookies to you. Again, this Privacy Policy does not cover the use of cookies by any third parties, and we aren’t responsible for their privacy policies and practices. Please be aware that cookies placed by third parties may continue to track your activities online even after you have left our Services, and those third parties may not honor “Do Not Track” requests you have set using your browser or device. 

We may use this data to customize content for you that we think you might like, based on your usage patterns, or to communicate with you regarding service updates, offers, and promotions. We may also use it to improve the Services – for example, this data can tell us how often users use a particular feature of the Services, and we can use that knowledge to make the Services interesting and provide you with the best user experience possible. We may also use this data to address network integrity and security issues, and to investigate and remediate violations of our Terms of Service and Acceptable Use Policies. 

Information Collected From Other Websites and Do Not Track Policy 

Through cookies we place on your browser or device, we may collect information about your online activity after you leave our Services. Just like any other usage information we collect, this information allows us to improve the Services and customize your online experience, and otherwise as described in this Privacy Policy. Your browser may offer you a “Do Not Track” option, which allows you to signal to operators of websites and web applications and services (including behavioral advertising services) that you do not wish such operators to track certain of your online activities over time and across different websites. Our Services do not support Do Not Track requests at this time, which means that we collect information about your online activity both while you are using the Services and after you leave our Services. 

Will Wish Share Any of the Personal Information it Receives? 

We do not rent or sell your Personal Information in personally identifiable form to anyone. We may share your Personal Information with third parties as described in this section: 

**Information that’s been de-identified:** We may de-identify your Personal Information so that you are not identified as an individual, and provide that information to our partners. We may also provide aggregate usage information to our partners (or allow partners to collect that information from you), who may use such information to understand how often and in what ways people use our Services, so that they, too, can provide you with an optimal online experience. However, we never disclose aggregate usage or de-identified information to a partner (or allow a partner to collect such information) in a manner that would identify you as an individual person. 

**Advertisers:** We allow advertisers and/or merchant partners (“Advertisers”) to choose the demographic information of users who will see their advertisements and/or promotional offers and you agree that we may provide any of the information we have collected from you in non-personally identifiable form to an Advertiser, in order for that Advertiser to select the appropriate audience for those advertisements and/or offers. For example, we might use the fact you are located in San Francisco to show you ads or offers for San Francisco businesses, but we will not tell such businesses who you are. Or, we might allow Advertisers to display their ads to users with similar usage patterns to yours, but we will not disclose usage information to Advertisers except in aggregate form, and not in a manner that would identify you personally. Note that if an advertiser asks us to show an ad to a certain audience or audience segment and you respond to that ad, the advertiser may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they were trying to reach. 

We may deliver a file to you through the Services (known as a “web beacon”) from an ad network. Web beacons allow ad networks to provide anonymized, aggregated auditing, research and reporting for us and for advertisers. Web beacons also enable ad networks to serve targeted advertisements to you when you visit other websites. Because your web browser must request these advertisements and web beacons from the ad network’s servers, these companies can view, edit, or set their own cookies, just as if you had requested a web page from their site. You may be able to opt-out of web beacon tracking conducted by third parties through our Services by adjusting the Do Not Track settings on your browser; please note that we don’t control whether or how these third parties comply with Do Not Track requests. 

**Affiliated Businesses:** In certain situations, businesses or third party websites we’re affiliated with may sell or provide products or services to you through or in connection with the Services (either alone or jointly with us). You can recognize when an affiliated business is associated with such a transaction or service, and we will share your Personal Information with that affiliated business only to the extent that it is related to such transaction or service. For example, when you complete a purchase using the Services, we share your submitting shipping address and phone number and any other necessary information with the shipping provider and the merchant in order to ship your purchase to you. We have no control over the policies and practices of third party websites or businesses as to privacy or anything else, so if you choose to take part in any transaction or service relating to an affiliated website or business, please review all such business’ or websites’ policies. 

**Agents:** We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you; for example, we may use a payment processing company to receive and process your credit card transactions for us when you make a purchase using the Services. Unless we tell you differently, our agents do not have any right to use the Personal Information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. Note that an “agent” may also be considered a “partner” in certain circumstances, and would be subject to the terms of the **“Information that’s been de-identified”** section in that regard. 

**User Profiles and Submissions:** Certain user profile information, including your name, photo, location, purchase history, items on your Wishlist, reviews you have written (including any photos you upload with such reviews), and the list of people you follow or that follow you, may be displayed to other users to facilitate user interaction within the Services or address your request for our services. Please remember that any content you upload to your public user profile, along with any Personal Information or content that you voluntarily disclose online in a manner other users can view (on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas, etc.) becomes publicly available, and can be collected and used by anyone. Your user name may also be displayed to other users if and when you send messages or comments or upload images or videos through the Services and other users can contact you through messages and comments. Additionally, if you sign into the Services through a third party social networking site or service, such as Facebook, your list of “friends” from that site or service may be automatically imported to the Services, and such “friends,” if they are also registered users of the Services, may be able to access certain non-public information you have entered in your Services user profile. Again, we do not control the policies and practices of any other third party site or service. 

**Business Transfers:** We may choose to buy or sell assets, and may share and/or transfer customer information in connection with the evaluation of and entry into such transactions. Also, if we (or our assets) are acquired, or if we go out of business, enter bankruptcy, or go through some other change of control, Personal Information could be one of the assets transferred to or acquired by a third party. 

**Protection of Wish and Others:** We reserve the right to access, read, preserve, and disclose any information that we believe is necessary to comply with law or court order; enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Wish, our employees, our users, or others. 

Is Personal Information about me secure? 

Your account is protected by a password for your privacy and security. If you access your account via a third party site or service, such as Facebook, you may have additional or different sign-on protections via that third party site or service. You must prevent unauthorized access to your account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password and/or other sign-on mechanism appropriately and limiting access to your computer or device and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account. 

We endeavor to protect the privacy of your account and other Personal Information we hold in our records, but unfortunately, we cannot guarantee complete security. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time. 

What Personal Information can I access? 

Through your account "Settings," you may be able to access, and, in some cases, edit or delete the following information you’ve provided to us: 

  * name and password
  * email address
  * physical address
  * location
  * phone number
  * gender
  * billing information
  * user profile information, including images and videos you have uploaded to the site

The information you can view, update, and delete may change as the Services change. If you have any questions about viewing or updating information we have on file about you, please contact us at [support@wish.com](mailto:support@wish.com). 

You may be able to add, update, or delete information as explained above. When you update information, however, we may maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records. You may request deletion of your account by clicking on “Delete Account” in your “Settings” and following the steps provided. Some information may remain in our records after your deletion of such information from your account. We may use any aggregated data derived from or incorporating your Personal Information after you update or delete it, but not in a manner that would identify you personally. 

Under California Civil Code Sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to contact us to prevent disclosure of Personal Information to third parties for such third parties’ direct marketing purposes. As stated in this Privacy Policy, we will not sell or share your Personal Information with non-ContextLogic companies for their direct marketing purposes without your consent. If you would like to submit such a request, please contact us at [privacy@contextlogic.com](mailto:privacy@contextlogic.com) or write us at ContextLogic Privacy Policy, 1 Sansome St. 40th Floor, San Francisco, CA 94104. 

What choices do I have? 

To opt-out of marketing communications you may use one of these convenient methods, but keep in mind some information may be needed to register with us or to take advantage of some of our features. 

  * **Electronic Promotional Offers.** If you do not want to receive emails from us regarding special promotions or offers, you may (1) follow the unsubscribe options at the bottom of each email; or (2) contact us at [privacy@contextlogic.com](mailto:privacy@contextlogic.com) and provide your email address along with the name of the newsletter from which you would like to unsubscribe. 
  * **Mobile Promotional Offers:** When you provide us with your mobile number for marketing purposes, we may send you certain marketing alerts via text message. Standard data and message rates will apply. If you no longer wish to receive mobile alerts from us, you can follow the instructions provided in those messages or otherwise reply STOP to any Wish alert. 
  * **Push Notifications:** When you use the App, you may receive push notifications. If you prefer not to receive push notifications, you may adjust your settings on your mobile device to control whether you want to receive these alerts 

You may also opt out of certain communications from us by changing your preferences under the “Settings” option of the applicable Service. Your instructions to limit the use of your information for these purposes will be processed as soon as reasonably practicable. Additionally, we are not responsible for informing third parties (including without limitation our third party service providers or partners) with whom we have already shared your personal information of any changes requested pursuant to this section, or for removing information from or causing information to be removed from the databases or records of such entities. 

What About Third-Party Content, Links, or Plug-Ins on the Services? 

The Services may have links to third-party websites or apps, which may have privacy policies that differ from our own. We are not responsible for the practices of such sites. 

The Services may also offer you the ability to interact with social plugins from social media sites, which may allow us and/or the social media site to receive data from or about you. In some cases, we may know that you clicked on a social plugin, such as a Twitter Follow button, or receive other information from the social media sites. Similarly, if you have previously provided personal information to a third-party operating a plug-in on the Services, then such third-party may recognize you on this Site. Your use of social network plugins is subject to each social media site’s privacy policy, which may be different from ours, so please read these policies carefully to understand their policies and your options. As with linked sites, we have no control over the information that is collected, stored, or used by social network plugins, and are not responsible for the practices of such sites. 

What About Information I Enter on Public Forums? 

Any information you may disclose on the Services, in blogs, on message boards, in chat rooms, or on other public areas on the Services or other third-party websites or apps that the Services may link to, becomes public information. Please exercise caution when disclosing personal information in these public areas. 

What if I have questions about this policy? 

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policies, please send a detailed message to [privacy@contextlogic.com](mailto:privacy@contextlogic.com) or write us at ContextLogic Privacy Policy, 1 Sansome St. 40th Floor, San Francisco, CA 94104. 

Last Updated: Aug 15, 2017
